Finding Aid for the Jesse Ely Wills Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- The Development of a Code of Ethical Standards for Psychology (7.085 Reprints) (Box 25)
- Notes on Proposed Symposium on Research in Psychotherapy
- A Memorandum of the Development of a Code of Ethical Standards (Box 25)
- for Psychotherapy
- Withdrawals
- Anderson, Barbara (Box 25)
- Bailey, R. Norman (Box 25)
- Balevre, Albert Park (Box 25)
- Barnett, Charles (Box 25)
- Bensberg, Gerard (Box 25)
- Berkshire, Judith Roger (Box 25)
- Berkson, Gershon (Box 25)
- Bialer, Irving (Box 25)
- (25 written on box lid) (Box 26)
- Boyce, Richard (Box 26)
- Brown, Ercil F. (Box 26)
- Broxton, June (Box 26)
- Butler, Marilyn (Box 26)
- Caldwell, Donald F. (Box 26)
- Carlisle, Mary E. (Box 26)
- Carroll, Heman (Box 26)
- Cobb, Jane H. (Mrs.) (Box 26)
- Conte, William (Box 26)
- Corley, Chloteal (Box 26)
- Cottle, Charles R. (Box 26)
- Crabtree, Robert C. (Box 26)
- Cullum, Edward Neely (Box 26)
- Drucker, Melvin (Box 26)
- Dupont, Henry J. (Box 26)
- Duwall, Mary I. (Box 26)
- Edwards, Mayme Louise (Box 26)
- Edwards, Richard W. (Box 26)
- Elser., Roger p. (Box 26)
- Engel, Mary (Box 26)
- Esser, Charles K. (Box 26)
- Flick, Leslie (Box 26)
- Foshee, James G. (Box 26)
- Fossick, Christine (Box 26)
- Gardner, William I. (Box 26)
- George, Ralph T. (Box 26)
- Gibson, Elsie M. (Box 26)
- Girardeau, Frederic (Box 26)
- Glassburner, Fred (Box 26)
- Gonce, James H. (Box 26)
- Goodgion, Ernestine (Box 26)
- Gordon, Alan (Box 26)
- Graham, Robert L. (Box 26)
- Green, Julian C. (Box 26)
- Gruether, Tresa (Box 26)
- Haeberle, Ann W. (Box 26)
- Hakin, Maurice A. (Box 26)
- Hall, Jon David (Box 26)
- Hargrove, Richard (Box 26)
- Harris, Cliff (Box 26)
- Haygood, Gordon B. (Box 26)
- Heber, Rick (Box 26)
- Rein, Harry (Box 26)
- Henninger, Harold E. (Box 26)
- Holley, Katie Dittmar (Box 26)
- Howell, Sara Mae Irick (Mrs.) (Box 26)
- Humphreys, F. Arthur (Box 26)
- Hylton, Harry L. (Box 26)
- Johnson, Dona Simpson (Box 26)
- Johnson, James Earl (Box 26)
- Johnson, Joseph c. (Box 26)
- Johnson, Ralph (Box 26)
- Jones, Charles (Miss) (Box 26)
- Katano, Nubuo (Box 26)
- Kenny, Thomas Joseph (Box 26)
- Kleu, James H. (Box 26)
- Koontz, Miriam (Box 26)
- Krainz, Ewald (Box 26)
- Lawler, Daniel L. (Box 26)
- Lewis, William L., Jr. (Box 26)
- Lewis, Wilbert W. (Box 26)
- Lovelace, Anna (Box 26)
- Leuchauer, Jarvis H. (Box 26)
- Lyles, Richard (Box 26)
- McClintock, Robert E. (Box 26)
- McConnell, John C. (Box 26)
- McDowell, Floyd E. (Box 26)
- McGinty, Lawrence E. (Box 26)
- Manis, Albert M. (Box 26)
- Marquis, Benjamin (Box 26)
- Marsh, Phyllis (Box 26)
- Matthews, Ophilia (Box 26)
- Mattioli, Michael J. (Box 26)
- Medlock, David (Box 26)
- Meek, Clinton R. (Box 26)
- Merrill, Edward C., Jr. (Box 26)
- Meyer, Robert J. (Box 26)
- Miles, Stanley (Box 26)
- Mitchell, Joy Ann Hays (Box 26)
- Mitchell, Walter M. (Box 26)
- Moore, Henry M. (Box 26)
- Morice, Herbert (Box 26)
- Moss, Beverly C. (Box 26)
- Moss, James (Box 26)
- Nafziger, Mary Katherine (Box 26)
- Nash, Judith (Box 26)
- Neblett, Mary Frances (Box 26)
- Neff, Harold Clifton (Box 26)
- Nelson, Frances Marie (Box 26)
- O'Beirne, Clifford (Box 26)
- O'Dell, M.J. (Box 26)
- Overture, C.L. (Box 26)
- Paar, Henry J. (Box 26)
- Palk, Bobbie (Box 26)
- Parkinson, Mary Elizabeth (Box 26)
- Parwati, Miss (Box 26)
- Pearce, Katherine E. (Box 26)
- Pettie, Robert E. (Box 26)
- Piers, Ellen V. (Box 26)
- Piety, Kenneth (Box 26)
- Poole, Finis W. (Box 26)
- Powell, Lucy D. (Box 26)
- Purcell, William E., Jr. (Box 26)
- Ram, Carlton (Box 26)
- Rasco, Elwyn W. (Box 26)
- Reece, C.L. (Box 26)
- Revel, Myriam A. (Box 26)
- Richardson, William P. (Box 26)
- Richmond, John D., Jr. (Box 26)
- Ringelheim, Daniel (Box 26)
- Rivera-Qlivencia, Pedro (Box 26)
- Robbins, Arthur (Box 26)
- Roberts, Joseph P. (Box 26)
- Russell, Frances M. (Box 26)
- Rutherford, Jeanne M. (Box 26)
- Sahai, Usha (Box 26)
- Santisteban, Ana H. (Box 26)
- Scarlett, Carl R. (Box 26)
- Schab, Fred (Box 26)
- Schlisinger, Myron (Mike) (Box 26)
- Sellers, William M. (Box 26)
- Shoemaker, Juanita M. (Box 26)
- Shore, Clement Wayne (Box 26)
- Sidwell, Dorothy M. (Box 26)
- Sivley, Robert (Box 26)
- Snow, Sadie M. (Mrs.) (Box 26)
- Soika, George (Box 26)
- Soyars, C.Y. (Box 26)
- Spears, William D. (Box 26)
- Spence, Clarence W. (Box 26)
- Spradlin, Joseph E. (Box 26)
- Stackfleth, Ellis L. (Box 26)
- Stanley, Rose S. (Box 26)
- Starkman, Stanley (Box 26)
- Stenzel, A.M. (Box 26)
- Stewart, P. (Box 26)
- Stoddard, Hugh T. (Box 26)
- Stocks, Elizabeth H. (Box 26)
- Story, Sylvia Parker (Mrs.) (Box 26)
- Tallant, Josephine (Box 26)
- Taylor, Charles A., Jr. (Box 26)
- Taylor, John Newton (Box 26)
- Taylor, R. (Box 26)
- Teng, Eugene Y. (Box 26)
- Tenner, Carl (Box 26)
- Tesseneer, Ralph A. (Box 26)
- Thompson, Fagan (Box 26)
- Thrasher, Carmie (Box 26)
- Throne, John M. (Box 26)
- Tillinghast, Burdette J. (Box 26)
- Tinder, Cecil K., Jr. (Box 26)
- Todd, Ronald E. (Box 26)
- Toole, Marjorie J. (Box 26)
- Turner, James (Box 26)
- Turpin, John (Box 26)
- Wade, John D. (Box 26)
- Walker, Gloria Sue (Box 26)
- Warner, Rodger J. (Box 26)
- Watts, Sue E. (Box 26)
- Weindenfeller, Paul G. (Box 26)
- Wilson, Ulrey K. (Box 26)
- Wood, John William (Box 26)
- Yo on, Tai Rim (Box 26)
- Zuidema, John E. (Box 26)
- "Nondirective Counseling," by Nicholas Hobbs (Reprints) (Box 26)
- Clinical Materials: Group Psychotherapy - Transcripts of Conferences (Hobbs, Session 5) (Box 26)
- Clinical Materials: Group Psychotherapy - Transcripts of Conferences (Hobbs, Session 4) (Box 26)
- Clinical Materials: Group Psychotherapy - Transcripts of Conferences (Hobbs, Session 3) (Box 26)
- Clinical Materials: Group Psychotherapy -Transcripts of Conferences (Hobbs, Session 2) (Box 26)
- Clinical Materials: Group Psychotherapy -Transcripts of Conferences (Hobbs, Session 1) (Box 26)
- Research, Columbia Meeting (Box 26, Folder 4.10)
- Research Symposium Mrs. Halpin (Box 26, Folder 4.11)
- Group Therapy (Mrs. Winston, #11) (Box 26, Folder 4.06)
- Group Therapy (Miss Lindroos, #16) (Box 26, Folder 4.06)
- Group Therapy (Miss Rabinowitz, #15) (Box 26, Folder 4.06)
- Group Therapy (Miss Messler, #17) (Box 26, Folder 4.06)
- Group Therapy (Miss Wehrle, #12) (Box 26, Folder 4.06)
- Group Therapy (Miss Rudolph, #13) (Black notebook) Axline – Prepracticum Group 1, C4 (Box 26, Folder 4.06)
- Group Therapy - Teacher Counselor Students (General) (Box 26, Folder 4.06)
- Group Analysis Sheet
- Self-Evaluation Checklist (Form TC-S) (Box 26)
- Group Leader Self-Evaluation Checklist (Box 26)
- Research - General Planning (Box 26, Folder 4.01)
- Incomplete Sentences Consistency Profile (Box 26, Folder 4.03)
- Group Therapy, Dr. Hobbs (July 12, 1948) (Box 26)
- Group Process Analysis Sheet
- (27 written penciled on box lid): (Box 28)
- Recording of Korner's Comments on Group Therapy. Teachers (Box 28)
- College, Columbia University (April 6) (Box 28)
- Recording of Korner's Comments on Group Therapy. Teachers (Box 28)
- College, Columbia University (April 14) (Box 28)
- Recording of Korner's Notes on April 19 Group Meeting (Box 28)
- Recording of Korner's Comments on Group Therapy (April 26, 1948) (Box 28)
- Teachers College, Columbia University (Box 28)
- Recording of Korner's Comments on Group Therapy (April 28) (Box 28)
- Teachers College, Columbia University (Box 28)
- Recording of Korner's Observations on Group Therapy (May 10 (Box 28)
- 1948), Teachers College, Columbia University (Box 28, Folder 1948)
- Recording of Intake Interview - Miss Rahenowitz and Miss (Box 28)
- Randolph - Teachers College, Columbia University (March 30 (Box 28)
- Group Therapy #11 (Case I-H 349) - A Case Study (Box 28)
- Envelope - Research Symposium, APA (1948) (Box 28, Folder 4.11)
- Research - American Institute of Research (General Correspondence) (Box 28, Folder 4.50)
- Research - A.I.R. Expense and Vouchers (Box 28, Folder 4.51)
- Research - A.I.R. Ediphone and Dictaphone (Box 28, Folder 4.52)
- Research- Incomplete Sentences Project (General Correspondence) (Box 28, Folder 4.15)
- Research - Group Therapy Planning (Box 28, Folder 4.20)
- Army Research Division Directory of Personnel (January, 1945) (Box 28, Folder 4.30)
- "The Development of a Procedure for Evaluating Officers in the United States Air Force," by Harley 0. Preston (Box 28, Folder 4.58)
- "Scientific Methods for Use in the Investigation of Flight Crew Requirements" (Box 28, Folder 4.585)
- Research- A.I.R. Incomplete Sentences Test (Pilot), Form B Final Examination, 382M, by Henry P. David (Box 28, Folder 4.60)
- Research- A.I.R. Incomplete Sentences Test (Pilot), Form A Incomplete Sentences Test and Answer Sheets (Box 28, Folder 4.61)
- Research - A.I.R. Captain Quality Rating Scale (Book in paperback form) Perceptualism: The Artist's Vision, by Hoyt L. Sherman. Columbus, Ohio: Ohio State University (1944) (Box 28, Folder 4.62)
- (Reprint) "Some Special Aspects of Psychotherapy in the Army Air Forces," by Lieutenant Colonel John M. Murray (read before the meeting of the Brief Psychotherapy Council, Institute for Psychoanalysis, Chicago, January 14, 1944) (Box 28)
- (Reprint) "Brief Psychotherapy in War Neuroses," by Lieutenant Colonel Roy R. Grinker and Major John P. Spiegel (presented before the meeting of the Brief Psychotherapy Council, Institute for Psychoanalysis, Chicago, January 14, 1944) (Box 28)
- (Reprint) "Ori So-Called War Neuroses," by Kurt Goldstein, Clinical Professor of Neurology, Tufts Medical School, Boston, Massachusetts (reprinted from Psychosomatic Medicine, volume 5, number 4, October, 1943) (Box 28)
- (Reprint) "Meningococcal Infection," by Lieutenant Colonel Earl R. Denny, Captain R.G. Bausche, and Captain M.A. Turner (reprinted from The American Journal of the Medical Sciences, volume 208, number 4, October, 1944) ---- (Box 28)
- (Reprint) "Purpuric Lesions in Meningococcic Infec~ions," by Major William G. Bernhard and Captain Arthur C. Jordan (reprinted from Journal Laboratory and Clinical Medicine, volume 29, number 273, 1944) (Box 28)
- (Reprint) "Measurement of Fusion Frequency of Flicker as a Test for Fatigue of the Central Nervous System," by Ernest Simonson and Norbert Enzer (reprinted from The Journal of Industrial Hygiene and Toxicology, volume 2~number 2,-February, 1941) (Box 28)
- (Reprint) "Age Differences and Sex Differences in Some Introvertive and Emotional Traits," by J.P. Guilford and Howard Martin (reprinted from The Journal of General Psychology, volume 31, pages 219-229, 1944r (Box 28)
- (Reprint) "A Neuropsychiatric View of German Culture and the Treatment of Germany," by Richard M. Brickner and L. Vosburgh Lyons (reprinted from The Journal of Nervous and Mental Disease, volume 98, number 3, September, 1943) (Box 28)
- Sample Tests and Questionnaires Clinical Materials (Group Psychotherapy - Transcript of Conferences - Pascal) (Box 28)
- Clinical Materials '(Group Psychotherapy - Transcripts of Conferences - Irion) (Box 28)
- Clinical Materials (The Case of Cpl. John C. Stammerer) Aviation Psychology Program (Analysis of the Duties of Aircrew Personnel) (Box 28)
- DG Army Individual Test (AGO: AIT-1) (Box 28)
- (DE 201C) Personal Inventory (Box 28)
- (DE 303A) Incompletes Sentences Test (Box 28)
- (DE 601A) Vocabulary Test (Box 28)
- Digits Forward and Backward (Box 28)
- DE507B (2) Record of Activity Interests (Box 28)
- Convalescent Personal Inventory (Box 28)
- DE407A Patients' Attitude Scale (Box 28)
- AFPDC Ltr 25-42 Subject: AAFPDC Psychological Test Manual (Box 28)
- C-H Adjustment Rating Scale (not entered in index to Test Materials-- No. being requested) (Box 28)
- DE 102A Wide Range Achievement Test (Box 29)
- DE 109A (Box 29)
- DE ll3A (Box 29)
- DE 114A Personal Data Sheet (Manual) P-S Experience Blank (Box 28)
- DE 201B (Box 29)
- DE 201C (Box 29)
- DE 205A (Box 29)
- DE 205BX2 Inventory of Present Reaction (Box 29)
- DE 207X1 (Box 29)
- DE 301A (Box 29)
- DE 406A Attitudes Inventory (Box 29)
- CE 519A Opinion Questionnaires (DE Group 499 - Attitudes) Critique (Suggestions by Patients) DE Group 400 - Attitudes (Box 28)
- DE 601A Intellectual Impairment Scale, Shipley (Box 28)
- DE 602A EMA (Box 29)
- DG 102A (Box 29)
- (28 written on box lid): (Box 29)
- (Offprints) "Guiding Child and Adolescent Development in the Modern School" (Offprints) Hutt, Max L. (Box 29)
- Tests: Kuder Preference Record (Box 29)
- Clinical Materials: The Case of Cpl. John C. Stammerer (Box 29)
- Explorations in Individual Counseling (2 folders) (Box 29)
- Correspondence: Rogers, Carl R. (Box 29)
- Correspondence: Laredo, Texas (Box 29)
- Personal: The Citadel (Box 29)
- Personal Letters (Box 29)
- Clarence Leuba's Syllabus for General Psychology (Pl 101-102), First and Second Semesters (1940-1941) (Box 29)
- First and Second Semesters (1940-1941) (Box 29)
- Bibliographies (Box 29)
- Attitude Scales (Box 29)
- Case Materials (Box 29)
- Book Notices (Box 29)
- Art (Box 29)
- Standardized Tests (Box 29)
- Remedial Reading (Box 29)
- Dissertation (Box 29)
- Class Notes - Psychology 401 (1940) (Box 29)
- Psychology 601 (Box 29)
- Psychotherapy (Box 29)
- Case Studies (Box 29)
- Revision - Characters (Box 29)
- Freshman Survey (Box 29)
- Ohio Farm.~ureau (Box 29)
- Tests. (Box 29)
- Adjustment Scales (Box 29)
- National Research Council (Box 29)
- A Student's Ph.D. Orals (Box 29)
- Klein's Higher Education (Box 29)
- Class Notes: Psychology 401-402 (Box 29)
- Army Extension Course (Box 29)
- Miscellaneous xeroxed copies (Box 29)
- Biography of an Attitude (Box 29)
- Interest Attitude Material (Box 29)
- History of Psychology (Box 29)
- Freshman Week (Box 29)
- Psychology 411 (Box 29)
- Education Survey (Box 29)
- Carnegie Foundation (Box 29)
- 618 - Clinical Tests (Box 29, Folder 618)
- Thurstone's Scale of Attitude Toward War (Box 29)
- Carl Roger's Seminar (Winter, 1940) (Box 29)
- (29 written on box lid): (Box 30)
- Bulletins - American Youth Commission (Box 30)
- Examination Questions (Box 30)
- Publications (Box 30)
- Psychology 411 Materials (Box 30)
- Toop's Motivation (Box 30)
- Correspondence (Box 30)
- Education 845 (Box 30)
- Ohio State University (Box 30)
- Report of Dr. Kircher's Lecture to Survey of Education 407 (Box 30)
- (November 8, 1939) [2 copies] (Box 30)
- Psychology 401 (Box 30)
- "Life, Liberty, and Property," by Alfred Winslow Jones (February, 1941) (Box 30)
- Stanford-Binet Tests (Box 30)
- Personal Papers (Box 30)
- Revision: Psychology and the New Education Alabama - Site Visits (Box 30)
- Alabama - Site Visits (Box 30)
- U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare Public Health Service (National Institutes of Health: Application for Mental Health Project Grant) Site Visits - Americus, Georgia Site Visits - Santa Barbara (Box 30)
- NIMH - Advisory Committee on Regional Conference (William Wright) (Box 30, Folder 9.16)
- NIMH- Site Visit to University of California MH 1253 - Site Visit to Hamburg State School and Hospital 9.4 NIMH - Grants Review Committee (Reports from Hobbs) Site Visits - Mental Health Projects Grants Review Committee 9.2 NIMH - Training Committee (2) (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Drews: The Gifted Child (Box 30, Folder 10.6)
- MacGregor: The Experiences of American Scholars In Counties of the Near East and South Asia (Box 30, Folder 10.7)
- Rinsland: Measurements, Marking, and Evaluations (Box 30, Folder 10.8)
- Smith - Educational Research: Principles and Practices (Box 30, Folder 10.9)
- Tiedmanf; J Theory of Occupational choice (Box 30, Folder 10.10)
- Preston:' Methods and Materials for Teaching the Mentally Retarded (Box 30, Folder 10.11)
- Boyer: Experimental Educational Psychology (Box 30, Folder 10.12)
- Bennett: Polydiagnostics (Box 30, Folder 10.13)
- Heisler and Garrison: The Psychology of the Elementary School Child (Box 30, Folder 10.14)
- Phillips, Duke, and DeVault Child Psychology (Box 30, Folder 10.15)
- Green: Measurement and Evaluation (Box 30, Folder 10.16)
- Adlerblum: Report on a Mental Hygiene Project (Box 30, Folder 10.17)
- Micheels and Karnes: Measuring Educational Achievement (Box 30, Folder 10.18)
- Brammer and Shostrom: Therapeutic Psychology for Counselors and Clinicians (Box 30, Folder 10.19)
- Barnes: Modern Educational Research (Box 30, Folder 10.20)
- Woollatt: Basic and Applied Education Research (Box 30, Folder 10.21)
- Kinzer: Ouline for a Text on Reading (No Title) (Box 30, Folder 10.22)
- Rothman and Berkowitz:, Recognizing the Disturbed Child (Box 30, Folder 10.23)
- (30 written on box lid): (Box 31)
- Baldauf: The School Psychologist (Box 31, Folder 10.24)
- Gordon: Human Development (Box 31, Folder 10.25)
- Gorlow and Katkovsky: Readings in Psychology of Adjustment (Box 31, Folder 10.26)
- Gibbs: Samples of Curriculum Materials for the Mentally Retarded (Box 31, Folder 10.27)
- Northern: Evaluation in Education (Box 31, Folder 10.28)
- Cook: Tests and Measurement (Box 31, Folder 10.29)
- Academic Prediction (Box 31, Folder 10.30)
- Kowitz and Kowitz: Human Development for Teachers (Box 31, Folder 10.31)
- Kephart: Education of the Slow Learning Child (Box 31, Folder 10.32)
- Zarrow, Bevan, Dukes, and Sheffington: Perceptual Guidance of the Child (Box 31, Folder 10.33)
- Lazarus: Adjustment and Personality (Box 31, Folder 10.34)
- Moss: IQs Below 80 (Box 31, Folder 10.35)
- Walsh-Davis: Interpretation of Research (Box 31, Folder 10.36)
- Piers: The School Psychologist (Box 31, Folder 10.37)
- Department of Psychology, Penn State: A Handbook of Educational Psychology (Box 31, Folder 10.38)
- Frandsen: How We Learn (Box 31, Folder 10.39)
- Sorenson: Psychology in Education (Box 31, Folder 10.40)
- Frostig: Education of the Child With Learning Difficulties (Box 31, Folder 10.41)
- Hammonds: Teaching and the Psychology of Learning (Box 31, Folder 10.42)
- Davis: Educational Measurements and Their Interpretation (Box 31, Folder 10.43)
- Mathis and Cotton: Psychology for Teachers (Box 31, Folder 10.44)
- Smith: The Gifted Child (Box 31, Folder 10.45)
- Hageny: Public School Discipline (Box 31, Folder 10.46)
- Stoddard: A Forward Look at Education (Box 31, Folder 10.47)
- Benjamin: The Future of Education - A Comparative View (Box 31, Folder 10.48)
- Herrick: The Dimensions of Future Development in Curriculum and Instruction (Box 31, Folder 10.49)
- Eichorn: Survey of Exceptional Children (Box 31, Folder 10.50)
- Mullen: Teaching the Educable Mentally Handicapped Child (Box 31, Folder 10.51)
- Gustad: The Choice of a Career in College Teaching or Teacher Motivation (Box 31, Folder 10.52)
- Foote: Health Problems of Exceptional Children (Box 31, Folder 10.53)
- Vickery: Education of the Mentally Retarded (Box 31, Folder 10.54)
- Smith and Wetzler: The Challenge of the Gifted (Box 31, Folder 10.55)
- Maw and Maw: Introduction to Education Through Human Development (Box 31, Folder 10.56)
- Ginott: Group Play Therapy and Disturbed Children (Box 31, Folder 10.57)
- Van Dalen: Understanding Educational Research (Box 31, Folder 10.58)
- Hirst, Wilma E. School Psychology (Box 31, Folder 10.59)
- Human Resources In Tennessee (Box 31, Folder 11.2)
- National Science Foundation: Research Programs (Box 31, Folder 11.3)
- Research Report: Counseling and Test Center, Ohio State (Box 31, Folder 11.4)
- Cincinnati Teachers (Box 31, Folder 11.10)
- Murray State College Project (Box 31, Folder 11.11)
- Baptist (Box 31, Folder 11.12)
- APA - OVR Institute (Box 31, Folder 11.13)
- Little Rock Institute (March, 1961) (Box 31, Folder 11.18)
- Tennessee M.D. Conference (Box 31, Folder 11.15)
- Educational Psychology (Box 31)
- Education 555A - Human Development and Guidance Grade Sheets (Box 31)
- Education 555A - Human Development and Guidance Preparation of Paper (Box 31)
- Education 555A - Human Development and Guidance Schedule for Course (Box 31)
- Education 555A - Human Development and Guidance: Hobbs' Notes (Box 31)
- Education 555A - Human Development and Guidance (Miscellaneous) (Box 31)
- Education 555A - Human Development and Guidance Agencies and Institutions in Nashville (Box 31)
- Education 555A - Human Development and Guidance List of Pamphlets of Children (Box 31)
- Education SSSA - Human Development and Guidance (Summer, 1959; 1960) (Box 31)
- Gifted Child Course (Box 31)
- 601 Basic Reading List (Box 31)
- Psychology 601 - Advanced Personality Theory (Box 31)
- Psychology 601 -Advanced Personality Theory (Papers 1957, 1958, 1959) (Box 31)
- Psychology 502 - Occupational and Educational Information Child Study Brochure (1960) (Box 31)
- (31 written on box lid): (Box 32)
- M-2529 Drug Study Material (Box 32)
- M-2529 1959-1960 Charges (Box 32)
- Grant M-2529 Purchase Orders (Box 32)
- Grant M-2529 Charges 148.1-2-3 (Box 32)
- Grant M-2529 Charges 148.4-5-6 (Box 32)
- M-2529 (Box 32)
- M-2529 62-63 Categories 4,5,6 (Box 32)
- M-2529 Category 148.4,5,6 (Box 32)
- Grant M~2529 Statement of Expenditures (Box 32)
- M-2529 Category 148.1,2,3 (Box 32)
- Account Book (black bound) (Box 32)
- M-2529 62-63 Categories 1,2,3 (Box 32)
- M-2529 62-63 Budget (Box 32)
- Grant 2529 Budget (Box 32)
- Miscellaneous (Box 32)
- Ethics (Box 32)
- Incoming Correspondence (Booklet) Ethical Standards for Psychology by Committee on Ethical Standards for Psychology, The American Psychological Association (May 21, 1951) [6 copies] (Box 32)
- Manuscript - Ethics and Public Responsibility 10.055 Subject Matter and Ideas Reported (Master Ditto Copies) Ethical Standards and Public Responsibilities (Box 32)
- Miscellaneous
- (32 written on box lid): (Box 33)
- Replies "Hold File" (Box 33)
- Correspondence A (Box 33)
- Correspondence B (Box 33)
- Correspondence C (Box 33)
- General and Miscellaneous: Cook, Stuart W. (Box 33, Folder 10.01)
- Correspondence D (Box 33)
- Correspondence E (Box 33)
- General and Miscellaneous: Edgerton, Harold A. (Box 33, Folder 10.01)
- Correspondence F (Box 33)
- Correspondence G (Box 33)
- Correspondence H (Box 33)
- Correspondence I (Box 33)
- Correspondence J (Box 33)
- Correspondence K (Box 33)
- General and Miscellaneous: Dr. Morris Krugman (Box 33, Folder 10.01)
- Correspondence L (Box 33)
- Correspondence M (Box 33)
- Correspondence N (Box 33)
- Correspondence 0 (Box 33)
- Correspondence P (Box 33)
- Correspondence Q (Box 33)
- Correspondence R (Box 33)
- Correspondence S (Box 33)
- Helen Sargent (Box 33, Folder 10.01)
- General Planning/Donald Super (Box 33, Folder 10.01)
- Correspondence T (Box 33)
- General and Miscellaneous - Tolman Committee (Box 33, Folder 10.01)
- Correspondence U (Box 33)
- Correspondence V (Box 33)
- Correspondence W (Box 33)
- General and Miscellaneous - Wolfe, Dael (Box 33, Folder 10.01)
- Correspondence X,Y,Z (Box 33)
- General and Miscellaneous - Yepsen, Lloyd (Box 33, Folder 10.01)
- General and Miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 10.01)
- Personnel (Box 33, Folder 10.02)
- Fiscal (Box 33, Folder 10.03)
- Plans (Box 33, Folder 10.04)
- Planning for September Meeting (Box 33, Folder 10.045)
- Incidents (Box 33, Folder 10.05)
- Reports (Box 33, Folder 10.06)
- Requests (Box 33, Folder 10.07)
- Standard Operating Procedures (Box 33, Folder 10.07)
- Codes of Ethics (Box 33, Folder 11.01)
- 1948 Report of the Professional Ethics Committee (Box 33, Folder 11.02)
- The History and Ethics of the Use of Human Subjects in Medical Experiments (Box 33, Folder 11.03)
- "An Oath Incorporating a Code of Ethics for Clinical Psychologists" (Box 33, Folder 11.04)
- Data on Ethical Problems from Questions on Tcg and Practice of Psychotherapy and Counseling (Box 33, Folder 11.09)
- 10575 No Incidents Reported (Box 33)
- Incidents to be Reworked (March 1 - ) (Box 33)
- Incidents to be Reworked (February 22 - February 28) (Box 33)
- Incidents to be Reworked (February 15 - February 21) (Box 33)
- Incidents to be Reworked (February 8 - February 14) (Box 34)
- Incidents to be Reworked (February 1- February 7, 1949) (Box 34)